hostfb.com 2014-11-08

# hostFB’s Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

At hostFB we are passionately committed to the privacy of our users. In this Privacy Policy we describe how private information is collected and how that is disclosed.

**Personal Information**

By personal information we mean your individual information such as First Name, Last Name, email address; and personal account information, such as desired login and desired password. During the registration, we may also collect some geographical and other type of information, such as your IP address, physical location, browser’s and computer’s screen properties, for possible further analysis and examination. By clicking “I accept. Create account” on registration page, you agree with hostFB’s Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy and grant us the right to collect the personal information about yourself. 

**The usage of collected personal information**

These are the only reasons why and when we may use your personal information: 

  * When sending newsletters (note, we are not going to bother you);
  * When sending notifications;
  * And when providing tech support.

**Disclosing of the personal information**

hostFB will not sell or share personal information submitted by you (including your personal info and content submitted through the services) to third parties except for those described in this Privacy Policy. An exception to this is the procedure of transferring of the submitted fan page content (iframe application, in particular) to Facebook by means of the Canvas URL. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may be changed by us from time to time. The changes become effective once they are posted to the hostFB’s site. If you continue using hostFB’s services you agree to be bound by amended Privacy Policy.
